Guide to the Human Rights Watch records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series 2: Country Files, 1978-1997
  - Conditions, 1989-1995 (Box 403, Folder 19)
    - Lingyuan Prison
      - General, 1989-1992 (Box 404, Folder 22)
        - Bhopal, 1989 (Box 420, Folder 2)
        - Communal Violence--Press, 1992-1993 (Box 420, Folder 3)
        - Communication w/Government, 1990-1992 (Box 420, Folder 4)
        - Contacts, 1988-1991 (Box 420, Folder 5)
        - Corruption, 1989 (Box 420, Folder 6)
        - Dams, 1989-1993 (Box 420, Folder 7)
        - Death Penalty, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 420, Folder 8-9)
        - Demonstrations, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 420, Folder 10-12)
        - Disappearances, 1989-1991 (Box 420, Folder 13)
        - Economic and Political Weekly, 1993, (3 folders) (Box 420, Folder 14-16)
        - Elections, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 420, Folder 17-18)
        - Embassy, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 420, Folder 19)
        - Foreign Relations, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 420, Folder 20-21)
        - Gandhi, Rajiv--Assassination, 1991 (Box 420, Folder 22)
        - General, 1979-1993, (12 folders) (Box 420, Folder 23-34)
        - Human Rights Commission, 1992 (Box 420, Folder 35)
        - Human Rights Violations, 1988-1993, (2 folders) (Box 420, Folder 36-37)
        - Human Rights Watch Arms Project--Report, 1994 September (Box 420, Folder 38)
        - International Human Rights Organizations, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 420, Folder 39-40)
        - Kashmir (Box 421)
        - General, 1989-1990, (8 folders) (Box 421, Folder 1-8)
        - Report--"Rape in Kashmir: A Crime of War", 1993 May (Box 421, Folder 9)
        - Killings, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 10-11)
        - Legal System/Texts, 1989-1990 (Box 421, Folder 12)
        - Military and Government, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 13-14)
        - Miscellaneous--India Related, 1993 (Box 421, Folder 15)
        - Missions/Visits, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 16-17)
        - National Human Rights Commission--Establishment, 1993 October (Box 421, Folder 18)
        - News Clips, 1990 April -1990 December (Box 421, Folder 19)
        - Opposition Abuses, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 20-21)
        - Police Abuses, 1992 (Box 421, Folder 22)
        - Political Opposition, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 23-24)
        - Press, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 25-26)
        - Prison Project, 1990-1991 (Box 421, Folder 27)
        - Prisons, 1989-1990 1992 (Box 421, Folder 28)
        - Publications--Miscellaneous, 1991-1994 (Box 421, Folder 29)
        - PUCL Bulletin--People's Union for Civil Liberties, 1991-1992 (Box 421, Folder 30)
        - Punjab, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 421, Folder 31-33)
        - Religious Violence and Unrest, 1989-1990 (Box 421, Folder 34)
        - Shahabuddin, 1991-1992 (Box 421, Folder 35)
        - Tamil Nadu, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 36-37)
        - Torture, 1991 (Box 421, Folder 38)
        - Trade and Aid, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 39-40)
        - Trade Unions Labor Rights, 1984 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 41-42)
        - United States
        - Congressional Advocacy, 1991-1992 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 43-44)
        - Policy, 1992 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 421, Folder 45-46)
        - Women's Issues, 1987-1992 (Box 421, Folder 47)
        - Indonesia (Box 422)
        - Asia Watch (AW)--Work, 1988-1993, (5 folders) (Box 422, Folder 1-5)
        - Abdullah Anshori Muhammad Toyib al Ibnu Toyib, 1987 (Box 422, Folder 6)
        - Aberson Sihaloho, 1997 (Box 422, Folder 7)
        - Access to Human Rights Groups (Indonesian Language), 1982 (Box 422, Folder 8)
        - Aceh, Sumatra
        - Article 19 International Centre Against Censorship, 1995 August (Box 422, Folder 9)
        - A Black Paper Documenting Javanese/Indonesian Crime of Genocide Against the People of Aceh/Sumatra, 1990 (Box 422, Folder 10)
        - Cases of Mahdi Yusuf and Mohamad Jafar, 1992 (Box 422, Folder 11)
        - General, 1989-1995, (12 folders) (Box 422, Folder 12-23)
        - Trials, 1991-1993, (11 folders) (Box 423, Folder 1-11)
        - U.S. Joint Publication Research Service--Democracy for Indonesia, 1960 (Box 423, Folder 12)
        - Adnan Buyung Nasution--Case, 1986-1988 (Box 423, Folder 13)
        - Aliansi Jurnalis Independent (Alliance of Independent Journalists), 1994-1995, (9 folders) (Box 423, Folder 14-22)
        - Aksi Duduk Burhanuddin, 1990 (Box 424, Folder 1)
        - Alex, David--Death--East Timor, 1997 (Box 424, Folder 2)
        - Amnesty International (AI) Reports, 1985-1988 1992 1994 1997, (2 folders) (Box 424, Folder 3-4)
        - Andreas Harsono--Journalist, 1997 (Box 424, Folder 5)
        - Anello, B.--Biographical Statement, 1989 (Box 424, Folder 6)
        - Arrests, 1989-1991 (Box 424, Folder 7)
        - Article 19 International Centre Against Censorship--The Press Under Siege: Censorship in Indonesia, 1994 November (Box 424, Folder 8)
        - Asia-Pacific Conference on East Timor (APCET) Report and Proceedings, 1994 May 31-June 5 (Box 424, Folder 9)
        - Bambang Beathor Suryadi--Trial, 1990 (Box 424, Folder 10)
        - Bambang Isti Nugroho and Bonar Tigor Naipospos--Trials, 1989-1990 (Box 424, Folder 11)
        - Bambang Subono and Isti Nugroho--Trials, 1989 (Box 424, Folder 12)
        - Bambang Supriyanto--Trial, 1997 (Box 424, Folder 13)
        - Bandung District Court--Students, 1989-1990 (Box 424, Folder 14)
        - Banned Seminars, 1996-1997 (Box 424, Folder 15)
        - Bishop Carlos Filipe X. Belo--East Timor, 1993-1996 (Box 424, Folder 16)
        - Bonar Tigor Naipospos and Bambang Beathor Suryadi--Trials, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 424, Folder 17-19)
        - Borneo Rain Forest--Western Canada Wilderness Committee, 1991 September (Box 424, Folder 20)
        - Children in Indonesia--UN, 1994 (Box 424, Folder 21)
        - Commission on Human Rights (KOMNAS)
        - General, 1993-1995 (Box 424, Folder 22)
        - Internal Report, 1996 September (Box 424, Folder 23)
      - Communication w/Government, 1989-1996 (Box 424, Folder 24)
      - Contemporary Indonesian Politics--Course Materials, 1986 (Box 424, Folder 25)
      - Corrrespondence
      - General, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 424, Folder 26-27)
      - Staff, 1988-1993 (Box 424, Folder 28)
      - Dadang Trisagongko--Case, 1992 (Box 425, Folder 1)
      - Death Penalty, 1986 1990 (Box 425, Folder 2)
      - Demonstrations, 1987-1993, (3 folders) (Box 425, Folder 3-5)
      - Detik, 1994 May-June (Box 425, Folder 6)
      - Directory of American Business in Indonesia, 1992 (Box 425, Folder 7)
      - Dresden, Germany Demonstration Against Visit of Suharto, 1995 (Box 425, Folder 8)
      - East Timor
      - Aditjondro, George
      - Case, 1994-1995 (Box 425, Folder 9)
      - Dili Massacre, 1991-1994 (Box 425, Folder 10)
      - Paper--Women's Experience in East Timor, undated (Box 425, Folder 11)
      - Aeta, 1990 (Box 425, Folder 12)
      - Agapito Cardoso--Political Prisoner, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 425, Folder 13-14)
      - Arrests, 1990 1993-1994 (Box 425, Folder 15)
      - Australia, 1992-1995 (Box 425, Folder 16)
      - Australian Council for Overseas Aid (ACOA), 1989-1990 (Box 425, Folder 17)
      - Background Papers and Situation Reports, 1989-1994, (2 folders) (Box 425, Folder 18-19)
      - Chronology, 1992 August -1995 June (2 folders) (Box 425, Folder 20-21)
      - Communication w/Government, 1992-1993 1997 (Box 425, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 425, Folder 23)
      - Demonstrations, 1989-1995, (3 folders) (Box 425, Folder 24-26)
      - Dili Massacre. 1991 (Box 426)
      - Accusation of Military, 1991 November (Box 426, Folder 1)
      - Amnesty International (AI)--News Release, 1991 November 14 (Box 426, Folder 2)
      - Asia Watch (AW)--"East Timor: The November 12 Massacre and Its Aftermath", 1991 December 12 (Box 426, Folder 3)
      - General, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 426, Folder 4-5)
      - International Commission of Jurists--"Blaming the Victims", 1992 February (Box 426, Folder 6)
      - Lembaga Bantuan Hukum Medan--Institute of Legal Aid, 1991-1992 (Box 426, Folder 7)
      - "Security Asistance: Shooting Incident in East Timor, Indonesia", 1992 February (Box 426, Folder 8)
      - Trials--Post (1991), 1992-1993 (Box 426, Folder 9)
      - Dili and Baucau Riots, 1995 (Box 426, Folder 10)
      - Disappearances, 1984-1994 (Box 426, Folder 11)
      - Documents on East Timor from PeaceNet and Connected Computer Networks, 1993-1995, (2 folders) (Box 426, Folder 12-12)
      - East Timor: A Bibliography, (1970-1994), 1995 (Box 426, Folder 14)
      - East Timor Human Rights Centre, 1996-1997 (Box 426, Folder 15)
      - East Timor News, 1990-1992 (Box 426, Folder 16)
      - "East Timor--Repression and Resistance: A Review of the 15th Year of Indonesian Occupation", 1990 (Box 426, Folder 17)
      - "East Timor: The Silence and Betrayal", 1994 March (Box 426, Folder 18)
      - Trials, 1991-1996, (6 folders) (Box 426, Folder 19-24)
      - Workers--East Timorese Workers in Java, 1991-1995 (Box 426, Folder 25)
      - Fernando de Araujo--Trial, 1992, (4 folders) (Box 427, Folder 1-4)
      - Fitun: A Bulletin on East Timor from Praxis, 1997 February (Box 427, Folder 5)
      - Francisco Miranda Branco--Trial, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 427, Folder 6-7)
      - General, 1986-1992, (9 folders) (Box 427, Folder 8-16)
      - General, 1991-1993 1997, (6 folders) (Box 428, Folder 1-6)
      - Gregorio da Cunha Saldanha--Trial, 1992 (Box 428, Folder 7)
      - Human Rights Organizations--Newsletters, 1991-1993 (Box 428, Folder 8)
      - Human Rights Violations, 1985-1990 (Box 428, Folder 9)
      - Indonesian Government, 1991-1992 1996 (Box 428, Folder 10)
      - International Organizations, 1986-1990 (Box 428, Folder 11)
      - Intimidation of Critics Abroad, 1996-1997 (Box 428, Folder 12)
      - Joao Freitas da Camara--Trial, 1992, (3 folders) (Box 428, Folder 13-15)
      - Joint Committee for the Defence of East Timorese, 1995 (Box 428, Folder 16)
      - Juvencio de Jesus Martins--Trial, 1992 (Box 428, Folder 17)
      - Jones, Sidney--Correspondence, 1992 (Box 429, Folder 1)
      - Kohen, Arnold S.--journalist, writer, 1988-1992 (Box 429, Folder 2)
      - Kommas Report--Liquisa Killings, 1995 (Box 429, Folder 3)
      - Land Issues, 1992-1993 (Box 429, Folder 4)
      - Missing Peace--Newsletter of the East Timor Talks Campaign, 1992 (Box 429, Folder 5)
      - Ninja Activity, 1994-1995 (Box 429, Folder 6)
      - Pope's Visit, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 429, Folder 7-8)
      - Prisons/Prisoners
      - Lists, 1988-1992 (Box 429, Folder 9)
      - Trials, 1991-1994 (Box 429, Folder 10)
    - Ramos-Horta, Jose--Statement, 1992 April 23 (Box 429, Folder 11)
    - Reconciliation Talks, UN Talks, 1990 1993-1995 (Box 429, Folder 12)
    - Refugees--Confidential Interviews, 1987-1988 (Box 429, Folder 13)
    - Timor Leste East Timor News, 1988-1989 (Box 429, Folder 14)
    - TimorLink, 1988-1989 1992-1997 (Box 429, Folder 15)
    - Timor-Oriental, 1990-1991 (Box 429, Folder 16)
    - Timor Oriental-Droits de l'Homme: les Violations Continuent ", 1985-1987 (Box 429, Folder 17)
    - United Nations
    - Decolonization Committee
    - Asia Watch (AW) Statements, 1990-1997 (Box 429, Folder 18)
    - Hearings on the East Timor Question, 1996 (Box 429, Folder 19)
    - Statements to, 1989-1997 (Box 429, Folder 20)
  - General, 1981-1995, (2 folders) (Box 429, Folder 21-22)
  - Indonesian Permanent Mission--Statement re, East Timor, 1992 July 28 (Box 429, Folder 23)
  - Testimony on Torture, 1987 (Box 429, Folder 24)
  - United States
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1988-1997, (4 folders) (Box 429, Folder 25-28)
  - Policy, 1994-1996 (Box 429, Folder 29)
  - Foreign Relations, 1990-1991 (Box 430, Folder 1)
  - Forum, 1993-1994 (Box 430, Folder 2)
  - Freedom of Association, 1989 (Box 430, Folder 3)
  - Freedom of Expression, 1988-1992 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box 430, Folder 4-6)
  - Tanah Untuk Rakyat, 1992 (Box 430, Folder 7)
    (Calendar Case)
  - Funu, 1995-1996 (Box 430, Folder 8)
  - General Background, 1984 1989-1992 1994-1997, (10 folders) (Box 430, Folder 9-18)
  - Greenpeace--"Indonesia's Proposed Nuclear Programme", 1992 May (Box 430, Folder 19)
  - Habibie and IPTN, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 20)
  - Himpunan Peraturan, 1988 (Box 430, Folder 21)
  - H.R. Dharsono alias Ayah Ton, 1986 (Box 430, Folder 22)
  - Human Rights (HR) Lawyers, 1990-1993 (Box 430, Folder 23)
  - Human Rights Monitors, 1989-1992 (Box 430, Folder 24)
  - Human Rights Violations, 1988-1991 (Box 430, Folder 25)
  - East Timor (Box 431)
  - Virgilio da Silva Guteres--Trial, 1991 December (3 folders) (Box 431, Folder 1-3)
  - Weschler, Joanna--Comments on Visit, undated (Box 431, Folder 4)
  - Xanana Gusmão--Maubere freedom fighter
  - General, 1990 1992 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 431, Folder 5-6)
  - Trial, 1993 (Box 431, Folder 7)
  - Wire Services, 1992 (Box 431, Folder 8)
  - Xavier, Bobby, 1998 (Box 431, Folder 9)
  - Indonesia
  - Editor, 1987 1990-1992 1994, (6 folders) (Box 431, Folder 10-15)
  - Elections
  - 1992 Election--General, 1992 (Box 431, Folder 16-18)
  - 1997 Election--General, 1997 May (Box 431, Folder 19)
  - Journalists, 1997 (Box 431, Folder 20)
  - Reporters sans Frontieres--"Indonesia: Pre-election Tension", 1996 June (Box 431, Folder 21)
  - Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 431, Folder 22)
  - ELSAM: The Institute for Policy Research and Advocacy, 1994-1996 (Box 431, Folder 23)
  - Environment, 1989-1991 (Box 431, Folder 24)
  - Executions, 1990-1994 (Box 431, Folder 25)
  - Huria Kristen Batak Protestan (HKBP)--Case, 1992-1995, (6 folders) (Box 432, Folder 1-6)
  - Indonesia News Service, 1987-1989, (6 folders) (Box 432, Folder 7-12)
  - Indonesia Reports, 1984-1997, (4 folders) (Box 432, Folder 13-16)
  - Index, 1995-1996 (Box 432, Folder 17)
  - Indonesian Human Rights Forum, 1991-1994 (Box 433, Folder 1)
  - Institute for the Defence of Human Rights Foundation
  - 1966 Constitution, 1966 (Box 433, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 433, Folder 3)
  - HJC Princen, Director, 1990 (Box 433, Folder 4)
  - International NGO Forum on Indonesia, 1988-1996, (5 folders) (Box 433, Folder 5-9)
  - Irian Jaya
  - Bibliografi Irian Jaya, 1993-1994 (Box 433, Folder 10)
  - Cases, 1988-1991 (Box 433, Folder 11)
  - Freeport Indonesian Co., 1992-1995, (2 folders) (Box 433, Folder 12-13)
  - General and 1993 Trip Report, 1989-1995 (Box 433, Folder 14-15)
  - Kabar dari Kampung, 1995 (Box 433, Folder 16)
  - Yayasan Pengembangan Masyarakat Desa Irian Jaya (YPMD-IRJA), 1994 (Box 433, Folder 17)
  - Iskandar bin Abdul Rasyid--Trial, 1987 (Box 433, Folder 18)
  - Isti Nugroho, 1989 (Box 433, Folder 19)
  - Judiciary, 1986-1987 (Box 433, Folder 20)
  - Killed Journalists, 1997 (Box 433, Folder 21)
  - Jacinto N. Raimundo Alves, 1992 (Box 434, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, David, "Indonesia 1965 The Role of the U.S. Embassy", 1995 July 12 (Box 434, Folder 2)
  - Juremi Adnan, 1987 (Box 434, Folder 3)
  - Killings, 1965
  - Data, 1981-1991 (Box 434, Folder 4)
  - General, 1989-1991 (Box 434, Folder 5)
  - Papers, 1965-1966 (Box 434, Folder 6)
  - Labor
  - Cases, 1992 (Box 434, Folder 7)
  - Concerns of International Labor, 1989-1990 (Box 434, Folder 8)
  - General, 1987-1993, (3 folders) (Box 434, Folder 9-11)
  - Generalized System of Preferences--Developments, 1993 (Box 434, Folder 12)
  - Labor and Press Rights Now in Indonesia, 1990 (Box 434, Folder 13)
  - Labor Laws, undated (Box 434, Folder 14)
  - Marsinah, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 434, Folder 15-16)
  - Serikat Buruh Sejahtera Indonesia (SBSI) (Indonesian Labor Welfare Union), 1993-1995 (Box 434, Folder 17)
  - West Java--Land Case, 1991-1994 (Box 434, Folder 18)
  - Workers Rights, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 434, Folder 19-20)
  - Land (Box 435)
  - Blangguan, Surabaya, 1987-1988 (Box 435, Folder 1)
  - Cases, 1988-1992, (4 folders) (Box 435, Folder 2-5)
  - Dedi Ekadibrata Trial--West Java--Land Protests, 1992-1993 (Box 435, Folder 6)
  - Kedung Ombo Dam, 1988-1991 1993-1994, (4 folders) (Box 435, Folder 7-10)
  - Lampung Province, 1989 (Box 435, Folder 11)
  - West Java--Land Cases, 1988-1993 (Box 435, Folder 12)
  - Legal System
  - General, 1992-1995 (Box 435, Folder 13)
  - Law and Political Liberty in Indonesia, 1989 (Box 435, Folder 14)
  - Legal Texts, 1989-1993 (Box 435, Folder 15)
  - Lembaga Bantuan Hukum (LBH) (Box 436)
  - Annual Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 436, Folder 1)
  - Dispute, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 436, Folder 2-3)
  - General, 1990-1991 (Box 436, Folder 4)
  - Madura, 1987-1989 (Box 436, Folder 5)
  - Maresh, Ben--Case, 1994 (Box 436, Folder 6)
  - Medan Riot, 1994
  - Chronology of Arrests, 1994 (Box 436, Folder 7-8)
  - Court Documents, 1994 (Box 436, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1994 (Box 436, Folder 10)
  - Trial Papers, 1994, (3 folders) (Box 436, Folder 11-13)
  - Megawati Soekarnoputri--politician, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 436, Folder 14-15)
  - Military and Government, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 437, Folder 1-2)
  - Missions/Visits, 1989 (Box 437, Folder 3-4)
  - Monitor Case, 1990 (Box 437, Folder 5)
  - Moeslim Abdurrahman (Muslim scholar), 1994 (Box 437, Folder 6)
  - Muzahar Muhtar--Trial, 1987 (Box 437, Folder 7)
  - "New Life" Prison Fellowship, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 437, Folder 8-9)
  - News Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 437, Folder 10)
  - NGO Activities banned by Military, 1990 (Box 437, Folder 11)
  - Nipah Dam/Madura, 1993-1995 (Box 437, Folder 12)
  - Non-Aligned Movement--Tenth Conference, 1992 September (3 folders) (Box 437, Folder 13-15)
  - Nuku Soleiman--Trial, 1993-1994 (Box 437, Folder 16)
  - Opposition Abuses, 1989-1991 (Box 437, Folder 17)
  - PDI Attack--Aftermath, 1996 (Box 437, Folder 18)
  - PEN Report--"Censorship, Silence, and Shadow Play", 1994 (Box 437, Folder 19)
  - Petisi 50--"Petition of Fifty", 1991 (Box 437, Folder 20)
  - PKI Prisoners--Death Penalty, 1990-1995 (Box 437, Folder 21)
  - Plesetan Case--Trial Documents, 1992 (Box 437, Folder 22)
  - "Political Islam in Indonesia", 1989 (Box 437, Folder 23)
  - Politics, 1993-1995 (Box 438, Folder 1)
  - Pope John Paul II--Visit--South Korea and Indonesia, 1989 (Box 438, Folder 2)
  - Pramoedya, 1991 (Box 438, Folder 3)
  - Prisons/Prisoners
  - General, 1987-1991 (Box 438, Folder 4)
  - Released Prisoners, 1991 (Box 438, Folder 5)
  - Treatment of ex-political Prisoners, 1989-1991 (Box 438, Folder 6)
  - Tuned to the Rhythms of Society: The Correctional System of Indonesia, 1980 (Box 438, Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1990-1993 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 438, Folder 8-9)
  - Ramone, David--Head of Student Senate, Sarjanawijayata University, 1992-1993 (Box 438, Folder 10)
  - Refugees from Indochina, 1990 (Box 438, Folder 11)
  - Res Publica Untuk Indonesia Yang Demokratis Dan Adil (draft), undated (Box 438, Folder 12)
  - Sahroni--Trial, 1987 (Box 438, Folder 13)
  - Sardjono alias Harun--Trial, 1987 (Box 438, Folder 14)
  - Schwartz, Eric--Interviews in Australia/Indonesia, 1986 March2-11 (Box 438, Folder 15)
  - Sei Lepan, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 438, Folder 16-17)
  - Shoot to Kill Policy by Police, 1993-1994 (Box 438, Folder 18)
  - Soebadio Sastrosatomo--Case, 1997 (Box 438, Folder 19)
  - Social Organizations/Law, 1987-1988 (Box 438, Folder 20)
  - Sri Bintang Pamungkas--Role in Ant-Student Demonstrations in Germany, 1995 (Box 438, Folder 21)
  - Students
  - Nuku Soleiman, 1993-1994 (Box 438, Folder 22)
  - Universitas Kristen Satya Wacana (UKSW), 1995 (Box 438, Folder 23)
  - "Suharto's Indonesia: Development and Death", AMPO, 1990 (Box 438, Folder 24)
  - Summary Reports, 1987-1991 (Box 439, Folder 1)
  - Surat Dakwaan--Trial Documents, 1996 (Box 439, Folder 2)
  - Syahrial Zakaria--Trial, 1987 (Box 439, Folder 3)
  - Tempo, 1983 1992-1994 June (12 folders) (Box 439, Folder 4-15)
  - Timor Gap Treaty, 1989 1991 1995 (Box 439, Folder 16)
  - Tjipto Ariyono--Trial, 1987 (Box 440, Folder 1)
  - Trade and Aid, 1989-1995, (3 folders) (Box 440, Folder 2-4)
  - Trials, 1986-1987 1996-1997, (2 folders) (Box 440, Folder 5-6)
  - United States
  - Congress--Generalized System of Preferences (Box 440, Folder 7)
  - Government Statements, 1989-1997 (Box 440, Folder 8)
  - Indonesian Relations, 1988-1991 (Box 440, Folder 9)
  - Policy, 1989-1991 (Box 440, Folder 10)
  - Wainggai, Dr. Thomas Wapai--Trial, 1989, (4 folders) (Box 440, Folder 11-14)
  - West Kalimantan--Case of Zainuddin Isman, 1997 (Box 440, Folder 15)
  - Women, 1986-1993 (Box 440, Folder 16)
  - World Bank, "Indonesia: Stability, Growth and Equity in Repelita VI", 1994 (Box 440, Folder 17)
  - Yap Thiam Hien (1913-1989), 1989 May 18 (Box 440, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified Materials, undated, (4 folders) (Box 440, Folder 19-22)
  - Japan (Box 441)
  - AMPO: Japan-Asia Quarterly Review, 1993-1994 (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) Conference, 1996 (Box 441, Folder 2)
  - Asia Watch (AW)--Work, 1990-1991 (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Students in Japan, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 441, Folder 4-6)
  - "Claims for Reparation Against Japan Coming from Injury Caused to Former POWs and Civilian Internees of the Netherlands", undated (Box 441, Folder 7)
  - Comfort Women--"Supplementary Explanation of the Recommendation on the Issue of ‘Comfort Women'"--Japan Federation of Bar Associations, 1995 (Box 441, Folder 8)
  - Communication w/Government, 1991-1992 (Box 441, Folder 9)
  - Contacts, 1992-1994 (Box 441, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence--General, 1989-1993, (2 folders) (Box 441, Folder 11-12)
  - Foreign Policy, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 441, Folder 13-15)
  - General, 1989-1992, (4 folders) (Box 441, Folder 16-19)
  - International Human Rights Organizations, 1989-1990 (Box 441, Folder 20)
  - Japan-Burma, 1991-1993 (Box 441, Folder 21)
  - Japan Civil Liberties Union (JCLU), 1988 (Box 441, Folder 22)
  - Koreans--Treatment of, 1988-1990 (Box 441, Folder 23)
  - Legal System/Texts, 1987-1989 (Box 441, Folder 24)
  - Military and Government, 1990-1992 (Box 441, Folder 25)
  - Missions/Visits, 1989-1994, (3 folders) (Box 441, Folder 26-28)
  - Official Development and Assistance (ODA), 1991 (Box 441, Folder 29)
  - Prison Project--Human Rights Watch (HRW), 1994 (Box 442)
  - Daiyo Kangoku
  - Igarashi, Mrs. Futaba--Articles, 1989 (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Japan Federation of Bar Associations (JFBA), 1989 1991 (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Detention Centers--Cases, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Drawings
  - For the Report, undated (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - From Mrs. Suzuki, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Prisons
  - Korea, undated (Box 442, Folder 6)
  - Lavinger Case, 1993-1994 (Box 442, Folder 7)
  - The Thai Women Case, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 8)
  - Varia, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 9)
  - Fuchu Prison
  - Government Brochure, undated (Box 442, Folder 10)
  - Interviews, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 11)
  - Government Materials, 1990-1991 1993 (Box 442, Folder 12)
  - Immigration/Detention
  - Clippings, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 13)
  - Intern's Paper, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 14)
  - Varia, Undated (Box 442, Folder 15)
  - Japan Human Rights Groups
  - Clippings, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 442, Folder 17)
  - Racism, undated (Box 442, Folder 18)
  - United Nations, 1984-1993 (Box 442, Folder 19)
  - United States--Department of State (DOS) Country Report--Japan, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 20)
  - Laws
  - Government Prison Bill, 1989 (Box 442, Folder 21)
  - Igarashi, Futaba, "Recent Moves to Change Laws Pertaining to the Treatment of Prisoners and Detainees in Japan", 1989 (Box 442, Folder 22)
  - Immigration, undated (Box 442, Folder 23)